A thousand pages on Camp David.
no black marker.
Any mention of him?
Sutherland hasn't worked for us
for the last ten months.
- Gotta be with some government agency.
- Not officially. he isn't.
This Broker
is about to control a sitting president.
The new mission. determine
the exact nature of their relationship.
Jay Batra was a great analyst.
- What about his boss?
- Ben Wallace.
Stellar career at FinCEN.
Helped bring down some big fish.
You have him leaking intelligence
to the press.
He's scared.
- I've seen you before.
- I don't think so.
He made. uh. contact with this reporter.
Isabel De Leon.
She writes for The Financial Register.
- A reporter? Strange.
- Yeah.
Doesn't sound like somebody
trying to sell classified intelligence.
It sounds like someone
with a story to tell.
- That seat's taken.
- We won't be here long.
I think he's telling the truth.
I'm looking at them now.
I need to call you back.
Five days ago. what happened?
He comes over and starts grilling me.
then destroys the hard drive
with the SARs.
I try to stop him. and he pulls a gun.
Says he's sorry that they made him do it.
I promise that if you come with me.
I will do everything in my power
to keep you safe.
- There's something I haven't told you.
- What?
That crypto wallet
belongs to Raúl Zapata and the LFS.
You predicted the attack on Pima 12?
And if what I suspect is true.
that would mean that--
Someone stateside funded the attack.
Hello?
I'm calling. Peter. because it appears
that you have something I want.
Or rather. someone.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
Send a text next time.
Sorry. Kopelson's got me on deadline
for this insider trading piece.
So I need a little favor.
You mean grunt work.
as the most junior reporter here?
No. as the reporter with the most energy.
- But it is grunt work.
- It's a learning opportunity.
What is this? More junk from the tip site?
Whoa. whoa. The tip site is not junk.
That's how I got my first byline.
Okay. most of it is junk.
But every so often. there's
a "there" there. You know what I mean?
Hey. I'm not asking you to stay late.
Just look it over when you can.
Please. with a cherry on top.
and a crisp $20 bill
on top of that cherry.
Okay.
There's a "there" there. right?
If I'm reading this correctly
and the dates are accurate.
then this guy. this Jay Batra.
basically predicted the terrorist attack
on Pima 12 a few days before it happened.
Yeah. Using suspicious activity reports.
And apparently. he still has them.
That's why he submitted to the tip site.
He says the companies
listed in that memo were involved.
A whistleblower with a paper trail.
Now that's a rare bird.
- Where is he?
- Istanbul.
- Turkey? So he's already on the run.
- He's scared for his life.
Then we need to be very deliberate
with next steps.
If he's legit. this story can be bigger
than the Panama Papers.
But if he's not. then--
- Mike. the FBI is on their way up.
- What? Why?
- They wanna talk to you.
- Give us a sec.
They can't be onto us already. can they?
Shit.
When you texted last night.
I reached out to my source at FinCEN
to verify the memo's authenticity.
He must have given them a heads-up.
- I gotta call Legal.
- Wait. wait.
Let me go where the proof is.
I'll find Jay
and get the rest of the reports.
To Istanbul?
That's not just dangerous. It's crazy.
We have no idea
what we're dealing with yet.
Mike. you told me yourself that crazy
and bold are the same exact things.
just different perspectives.
Let me do this.
Now. before they shut us down.
Keep in mind. I am going.
whether you okay this or not.
Be careful.
And keep receipts.
Oh. thank you.
Don't mention it.
May I help you?
FBI.
Friends of yours?
Yeah. Come on.
Just give me a second.
Sit tight. I'll be right back in a second.
All right.
I got four missed calls from The Broker
while we were in the air.
- He's not tracking you on that thing?
- No. I cloned the SIM.
The original one he gave me
is back in D.C.
Four calls? He's eager to talk.
What does he want with our boy over here?
Jay told me the suspicious
activity reports he took off with
connect the LFS attack on Pima 12
with some American shell corporations.
The Broker probably knows about it.
- You think one of those companies is his?
- I think all of them are.
Look. Raúl Zapata and the LFS
are a small terrorist organization
that have been dormant
for. what. a decade now?
More.
Now they're back on the scene
with enough military equipment and money
to swat a commercial airliner
out of the sky?
What are you implying?
How does a bush-league terrorist group
go pro all of a sudden?
And who do we know
that can facilitate that?
Same man who facilitated
the UN attack last year.
Exactly. It's got
The Broker's fingerprints all over it.
So Jay connected the dots
he wasn't supposed to.
You said Jay leaked his findings
to the press. Which outlet?
The Financial Register.
Oh shit.
It wasn't Mike Fonseca. was it?
Our New York field office
was trying to question him last week.
- The reporter's name was Isabel De Leon.
- Let me get somebody on her.
Realistically. we're not gonna get
those documents back anytime soon.
Not without a court order.
- It's him.
- Answer it.
Put it on speaker.
Hello?
You haven't been answering my calls.
Yeah. I was in the air.
Just landed back in the States.
I'm in New York.
Oh. welcome home.
Did the package arrive with you safely?
Yeah. Yeah. I got him.
Good.
I'll send details
as to where he's to be dropped off.
I trust you can handle that?
Peter?
No. No. that's not how this is gonna work.
Oh? And how do you imagine it happening?
Enlighten me.
You taught me a lesson once on value.
Now. this package
clearly has some big value to you.
so I'm not gonna be handing him over
to you no questions asked.
Do I have to remind you
of our arrangement?
I honored that deal when I broke into
the UN and got you those documents.
You don't own me forever.
I have some security footage
that might change your tune.
Then use it.
But you won't.
'cause then I'll have no value to you.
Let me propose something new.
Ever play the game Go Fish?
Not since I was a kid. no.
Well. I'm asking you for a jack.
A single expendable card.
One I know you have.
So you give him to me.
and then you ask me for a card.
And I've got a damn near whole deck
in my hands.
So you're suggesting. uh… a trade?
I'm suggesting a mutual benefit.
I get what I want. you get what you want.
Look. this analyst
that you want me to hand over.
I need to know
I'm not putting his life in danger.
Of course not.
What we're dealing in here
is an exercise in economics.
- A value exchange. nothing more.
- What if I say "go fish"?
Then we'll move on to a different game.
One with deadlier stakes.
Think about it.
I'll be in touch.
Welcome back.
I figured you'd be hungry.
so I ordered some--
Onion rings? It's 10:00 a.m.
What's wrong with you?
What are you. my mother?
These are the best in the city. Try one.
- Here you go. hon. black.
- Thanks. Fran.
Hey. you want me
to stow your luggage behind the bar?
- Yes. please.
- Okay.
This pile are suspicious activity reports
of all the companies
whose cash withdrawals
match the cash flow
that went into this pile.
Records for a crypto wallet
known to fund La Fuerza de La Soberanía.
The LFS?
Jesus. this kid really did have the goods.
Yeah. and you tried
to talk me out of going.
No. I just made you fight for it.
Builds character. You can thank me later.
How'd Jay seem?
- Terrified.
- He should be.
He killed his boss and fled the country.
The FBI grilled me for hours
after you left.
He thinks the Feds
are trying to kill him. not arrest him.
- That's a little paranoid.
- Maybe. maybe not.
As soon as I got Jay talking.
this guy who tried to hit on me
the night before showed up.
Recognize him?
Yeah. that's the guy wanted
for kidnapping Ashley Redfield's daughter
a couple of years ago.
Peter Sutherland Jr.
- He was exonerated though.
- He was.
Which begs the question. what's a former
FBI agent doing with our source?
They don't send
a guy like him for nothing.
- You thinking cover up?
- I don't know what I'm thinking.
A mentor once taught me
never to assume anything.
But Jay hasn't messaged me in 24 hours.
and I'm starting to worry.
- Is there anything in the tip site?
- Not yet.
- Maybe he went back underground.
- Yeah. maybe.
All right.
Well. we certainly got enough here
to start digging in.
- What's our next move?
- Why are you asking me?
You're the one that has decades more
forensic accounting experience than I do.
- Oh. now you're just making me sound old.
- Decades and decades more experience.
Don't act like you haven't been gaming
this thing out the whole flight home.
You got good instincts.
Use them.
What's next?
Okay. So I've been looking
for common threads.
and I found a pretty big one.
Vernon Tyvek? Who's that?
The compliance officer
who filed all the SARs that Jay handed us.
until he was fired two months ago.
- Do you ever sleep?
- That's what coffee's for.
The only problem
is that these banker types.
they have a LinkedIn
or a profile page somewhere.
But Vernon. he's not really online.
so I'm having a hard time
tracking him down.
- How old is he?
- Around my age. Why?
- Fran. I'mma borrow this.
- Yeah.
What century is that even from?
2019. the last year they printed 'em.
What? You'd be surprised
how often this comes in handy.
There's no way he's in there.
No. but if his parents are my age.
they might be.
And he's got a unique last name.
It's ringing.
Would you take a lie detector test?
Yes. please. I got nothing to hide. man.
I just want my life back.
I'm just a low-level analyst.
for Christ's sake.
I don't need to get involved
in… whatever the hell this is.
All right. You've had a long flight.
There's a shower upstairs. fresh towels.
Wash up. We'll order some food in.
Okay. but aren't we going to. like. an FBI
office or somewhere with real security?
We're not just gonna hang out
at some rando's house. are we?
This place isn't random. Jay.
It's ours. okay? You'll be safe here.
Okay. it's just…
Look. I get it.
You got questions.
I promise you. we'll get you answers.
But right now. we have to talk.
so just. uh. go get cleaned up. you know?
Okay.
Hey. uh. Peter.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Of course.
- I think the kid's telling the truth.
- Me too.
We should fold him in.
He found a needle in a haystack once.
What's to say
he can't recreate the evidence.
given more time and resources?
You're saying we walk away
from The Broker's offer.
a chance to finally ID him
and maybe get the evidence
to put him away?
I'm saying it's a rigged game
using his rules. We don't have to play it.
- We have the leverage here.
- Do we?
All we know is that he wants Jay.
But even Jay doesn't know why.
Then what do you propose? Use him as bait?
After everything that happened
at the UN last year?
We sat on every building he ever touched.
reviewed hundreds of hours
of security tape.
and even with all of that.
we've never been closer
to setting our sights on this guy.
Aiden. what does that tell you?
We can't just hand Jay over to him.
What if The Broker kills him?
This is an opportunity we cannot pass up.
What if we don't do either?
What was your favorite part?
Well. I kind of liked the part
where the kid.
he found the treasure map in the chest
of the old pirate Billy Bones.
Mm-hmm.
It was kind of sad that he died
but also cool and mysterious.
Like the adventure was just starting.
- Go on. then.
- Yes.
Yes.
I understand.
But we already had this conversation.
and you wouldn't agree to my price.
You chose local hires in Istanbul.
and they created a mess…
with more exposure and more risks.
Which means that yesterday's price
is no longer today's price.
No.
Triple.
Send over the details then.
and I'll get started this evening.
You have to work again?
I do.
But we get to go to New York this time.
- Can we see the Statue of Liberty?
- We can. and we will.
Now…
You leveled up in the last session. right?
Yeah.
All right.
Let's see what further dangers await.
- Yeah?
- Now's the time for choosing. Peter.
Is there a deal to be made.
or are we both gonna
be walking away empty-handed?
Yeah. I'd like to. uh. propose something.
Well. excellent news.
I'm listening.
I want names of corrupt agents
within the FBI and the CIA.
Is that how you justify working with me?
Putting a few bad guys away
so you can sleep better at night?
It's not about you.
Okay? I… I can't just misplace
a FinCEN agent that's in my custody
without someone to blame it on.
so I need names. I need dirty agents.
People I can give my bosses
so they don't think I'm crooked.
Well. luckily for you.
names are my stock-in-trade.
Will two suffice?
- Ten.
- Ten?
Don't overplay your hand.
If I was overplaying my hand.
you would've hung up by now.
Now is the time for choosing.
Four.
Five.
Five?
You know you're a tough little
son of a bitch when you decide to be.
Good for you.
Five it is.
I need one of the names now.
with evidence.
so I can verify the ID.
So you don't trust me
to deliver the goods. Peter?
If you were in my shoes. would you?
I'll send one over now.
The rest. upon delivery.
Deal?
Deal.
We get him?
Only if he's in seven different cities
all at the same time.
Fuck.
Is that…
He sent the name.
- You're not my food.
- Vernon Tyvek?
I'm Mike Fonseca
from The Financial Register.
This is my colleague. Isabel De Leon.
We were hoping to ask you some questions.
How'd you get this address?
Your mother was kind enough
to lend a hand.
She'd appreciate a call
every once in a while. you know.
- May we come in?
- What's this all about?
Your time at Walcott Capital Bank.
We learned you parted ways with the bank.
And we were hoping you would help us
understand why the sudden exit.
Simple. downsizing.
- Got a good exit package though.
- I see you're enjoying your time off.
- Yeah. Anything else?
- Yes.
The story we're working on involves
a number of suspicious activity reports
that you filed
during your time at the bank.
We were hoping
you could verify their authenticity.
- Where did you get those?
- Sorry. we don't reveal our sources.
Which is how you know anything
that you share with us
will be treated
with strict confidentiality.
Confidentiality?
Uh. listen.
I… I really can't be talking to you guys.
We understand. We do.
We can go away and never come back.
But you'll have to tell us
where to go instead.
or the trail for the reports
ends here on your doorstep.
Leaving you with some
tough questions to answer
for the next people who come knocking.
Okay. fine. let me see 'em.
Anything will help us.
If you notice a certain pattern
with the companies--
My job was to identify bogus transactions.
not run investigations.
- That's FinCEN's job.
- Yes. I understand.
But looking at the SARs altogether.
is there anything that jumps out at you?
Not really.
They're all textbook shell companies.
Except for this one.
Heroes In Healing?
Yeah. they're a nonprofit
for injured vets.
which seemed legit
until I started flagging their activity.
Could you expand on that. please?
Rapid movement of funds. incomplete
or false documentation. smurfing.
Know what that is?
Yes. large transactions broken down into
multiple smaller ones to avoid detection.
Mr. Tyvek. can you help us
fill in the gaps?
Please. we could really use
your expertise.
You asked me to point a finger. I did.
I… I really can't get deeper than that.
Right. We understand.
- Thank you for your time. Vernon. really.
- Don't mention it.
Like. literally. don't.
- Nonprofit for injured vets?
- Heroes In Healing.
- Do you know it?
- No. but I have a contact who might.
What. another name from the phone book?
No. an old source from inside the Beltway.
I'll try and set up a meeting.
Maybe they'll be able
to clarify some things.
I'll look into the nonprofit.
see what I can find.
No. I'm gonna drop you home.
You must be exhausted.
- What?
- Yeah.
How could you think about sleep
at a time like this?
A thousand pages on Camp David.
no black marker.
- Any mention of him?
- You want…
Special Agent Shigeru Ando.
Can't believe we were about
to make him section chief.
He's definitely dirty.
There's at least four more
where he came from.
Only if we give him Jay.
Right?
Say we play along a little longer.
We could root out some of the biggest
intelligence breaches in decades.
Agent Ando is just the tip of the iceberg.
There's no telling
what other names he'll hand over.
what other departments
they'll be embedded in.
She's not wrong.
We play this right. Record the exchange.
His list for the analyst.
That's a federal charge.
Conspiracy. racketeering.
We could put him away for good. Peter.
Not a year from now. today.
And you could get your life back.
- What about Jay's safety?
- We can protect him.
I'll put a few HRT units together.
- You two will never leave our sight.
- No. we need to keep this small.
There's no telling
what other names are on that list.
Anyone could be compromised.
I know some Joint Terrorism
Task Force guys out in Jersey.
They owe me a favor. They're solid.
You're not listening.
I promised Jay that I would keep him safe.
Now you're asking me to dangle him
in front of the biggest shark we know?
I think you're under the illusion
that we have other options.
We don't.
The analyst is our best path forward.
I'm not putting him at risk
because a bunch of people
who aren't Jay agreed to it.
It's not our choice to make. It's his.
What if Jay says no?
Then he says no.
- Peter.
- It's his decision. Catherine.
Hey.
- Hey.
- Where'd you find those?
It was just lying around.
Trying to keep my mind focused.
Solve something
so I don't spiral out. you know.
Yeah.
Listen…
Everything okay?
You've been kept in the dark
on some things.
Okay? I think you deserve to know
what's being discussed down there
and. uh… how you fit into it all.
Okay.
About a year ago. I was working a case.
And…
I made a deal with the devil.
He was an intelligence broker.
and he had details
about a terror plot at the UN.
The arrangement that I made with him.
it saved a lot of lives. but…
it also came with a pretty big IOU.
Now that same guy.
he wants to collect on his debt.
He wants you. Jay.
What do you mean?
What do you mean. he wants me?
Wait. who even is this guy?
Can't you just arrest him?
It's not that easy.
This guy. he's extremely careful
about what he says and who he says it to.
Peter. you said I'd be safe here.
I should've just listened to the reporter
and tried to get asylum.
The good news is. you have options.
Option one. we can move you
into the Witness Protection Program.
We can put you someplace safe.
and you can start a new life.
Now that's low risk.
but it's also low reward.
'Cause you'll always
be looking over your shoulder.
But option two
is you let us use you
to draw this guy out into the open.
Okay. now that's high risk.
but it's also high reward.
Because once
we arrest this guy. he's gone.
Okay? He'll never bother you again.
It's just that
there are a lot more unknowns.
And that's it? Two options?
Okay. what's the bad news. then?
The bad news
is this is your decision to make.
No one else can make it for you.
This is your life.
What kind of choice is that?
I just don't wanna die.
And I can't keep running either.
- What would you do if you were me?
- I'm not you.
No. just say you were. What would you do?
Peter. my whole life
is just about numbers.
Adding them up. making sure they fit.
But I don't know what the risks are
'cause I've nothing to weigh them against.
So just humor me for a goddamn second
and just tell me what would you do.
Please.
If there was a way that I could've gotten
this guy behind me before now.
I would've done it.
But that's me.
So you're saying I should--
No. I'm not saying you should do anything.
You asked me what I would do.
and I told you.
Now what you need to do.
figure out the percentages.
and we'll stand by
for your decision downstairs.
Isabel?
Isabel. Mike's been calling for you.
- Oh. he has?
- Yeah.
Said he's just finishing up
with the source
and wanted you to meet him
at the place with the good onion rings?
Okay.
Oh. and the Anderson file.
He wants you to bring it.
The Anderson file?
Are you sure that's what he said?
Yeah. That's what he said.
…tears falling like rain
All the dreams. they had to change…
- Here you go.
- Thanks. Fran.
Hey. what's the deal with the jukebox?
You trying to drive away us regulars?
Sorry. it's a bar crawl.
Barely even sounds like music.
No soul.
Pardon me?
I said no soul.
This crap we're listening to.
Yeah. I hear you.
I don't wanna throw rocks
at the next generation.
but this just sounds. um.
overprocessed. right?
Not my taste.
What's your poison?
IPA.
No. no. I mean music.
What do you like?
Journey. Eddie Money. Santana?
Yeah. they're all good.
What about Bon Jovi?
Oh. Bon Jovi for sure.
You know. I saw them in '88
in the Jersey Syndicate Tour. Amazing.
"Livin' on a Prayer."
That is a song you can drink to.
In my case. too much. but yeah.
Know what messes with your head?
Is hearing the songs of our youth
in commercials now for boner pills.
That's how you know you're getting old.
Well. what are you gonna do?
It's their world now.
You know what I say to that?
- Screw it.
- Huh.
Seriously.
You want Bon Jovi?
Go get some Bon Jovi on me.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
You know what to do.
There it is.
The Jersey Syndicate Tour rides again.
I queued up
"Don't Stop Believin'" for you after.
- Yes.
- Cheers.
Oh. hey. sorry.
Could I get some quarters
for the meter out front?
Here you go.
Another parking ticket
and my wife will have my tit in a wringer.
Oh. we don't want that.
Union's been on strike
He's down on his luck. it's tough
So tough
Gina works the diner all day
Working for her man
She brings home her pay. for love…
- Hey. Mike. you okay?
- I'm…
Hey. Mike?
Hey… hey. buddy!
Somebody call 911!
- Yeah.
- So. what do you say. Peter?
Have I won over your trust yet?
The name you sent checked out.
so as long as the others are just as good…
Well. of course.
So it sounds like we're on then. yes?
Yeah.
Yeah. we got a deal.
Excellent.
And I have your word
that you'll come alone?
Just you and the trade in question.
As long as I have your word
that no harm will come to him.
Well. then we're ready to meet.
Midnight.
59th Street Bridge.
I'll have you picked up. And. Peter.
I'm looking forward to seeing you again.
Step to the side.
- Ma'am. Stay back.
- It's okay.
He's my friend. What happened? Is he okay?
- You knew him?
- I was just with him. What happened?
He have a history of high blood pressure.
hypertension. heart disease. AFib?
I don't know. I was just with him today.
He was fine. He was totally fine.
Is he gonna be okay?
I'm back.
Hey.
Oh. what'd you get? Burgers?
- Subs.
- Oh.
How was your work?
What do you mean?
Each time you go
on a new business assignment.
I assume there are aspects of it
that are different.
Different problems. obstacles.
I love the questions you ask. I really do.
Yes.
This new assignment
comes with certain unique challenges.
That's how we measure ourselves.
That's right.
What page you on?
Two hundred and six.
Wow. That's great.
- I knew you'd love this one.
- Yeah. it's not too bad.
What's your favorite part so far?
The part where White Fang
gets captured by the hunters.
Oh yeah.
Here. check. Let's go.
Standing by.
- Let's go.
- I got you.
Peter. Jay.
- This is JTTF Commander Chip Highmore.
- Good to meet you.
He and his men will be following
your every move in the trail van.
- Thanks for helping us out tonight.
- No sweat.
Anything for Catherine.
Good luck out there. yeah?
You boys are in good hands. We got you.
Thank you.
- What?
- Nothing.
Damn right. nothing.
Here. take this.
It's new tech out of DARPA.
Works by frequency hopping.
making it impossible for surveillance
countermeasures to pick it up.
- Is that like a radio?
- Kind of.
Only works one way. though.
so they can hear us. we can't hear them.
Remember. we need the list
of names in exchange for Jay.
Once that happens. Catherine.
Highmore. and his team can swoop in.
Don't push too hard.
We don't want him getting suspicious.
We don't wanna blow the case
on entrapment.
Got it.
And. Jay. same rules apply.
plus one extra.
You can't let on
that you're being followed.
So no wandering eyes.
You play confused. even angry.
I know that there's a lot riding on this.
but we finally get a chance
to hear this intel broker's voice
and how he operates in live time.
That is all thanks to you.
So… now you just go get him.
For all of us.
Yes. ma'am.
Levels good?
Aiden. you picking this up?
Clear as a bell. I got him.
Peter.
Yeah.
I'm… I'm scared. man.
That's good. Okay? Use it.
We're not supposed to be
on the same team anyway. Remember?
Right. Hence the. uh…
Yeah. exactly.
Hey.
You'll be okay.
Against the car.
Honestly. didn't think you'd show.
- Where we going?
- You'll see soon enough.
They're headed westbound.
Copy. Signal's still good.
Shit. you don't think the tunnel
goes all the way through. do you?
Roma. call the USGS
and see if the NJT plugged--
Hey. wait.
Where the hell are we?
Hello. Peter.
You're looking well.
- Can't say the same for you.
- Yeah.
A little bit of a stomach bug.
It'll pass.
And you must be the elusive Jay Batra.
You're a slippery one.
Didn't really have a choice.
Hmm.
Held up my end of the deal.
Now. where's the list of names?
Now. don't be rude.
You're talking about our new friend
like he's some sort of prize
to be bargained for.
Mr. Batra. I'm curious.
What do you know about me?
What has Peter told you?
- I told him--
- No. no. no.
I wanna hear it from him.
Well. he said you were dangerous.
Oh.
Please.
But that you wouldn't hurt me
'cause you always kept your word.
Which is more than I can say for him.
So…
It's true.
Peter is not one
for good first impressions.
but it was right
for him to bring us together.
Now. tell me. how exactly did you do it?
Do what?
The SARs.
I mean. your job is to untangle
financial webs and puzzles.
but it is your particular knack
for piecing them back together
that has me intrigued.
Just good with numbers. I guess.
Oh.
It's quite a talent.
I'm curious to see
more of that ability in action.
Okay. we done?
The list.
Four additional names.
with evidence. as we agreed.
But first…
take a moment.
Drink it all in.
Because this is what
true partnership looks like. Peter.
You scratch my back. I scratch yours.
everybody gets what they want.
including our new friend here.
- Are we happy?
- Yeah.
We're on. Go. go. go!
Stop here.
No. no. no.
Not yet.
- We had a deal.
- Yes. we did.
But allow me one more moment.
For what?
Turn off the engine
and get out of the vehicle now!
Get back! Now--
What was that?
That was the sound of us
learning a very difficult lesson.
Don't move your fucking hands.
I offered you the carrot. Peter.
and you lied to me.
So let me remind you of the stick.
You exist in this world at my pleasure.
As does any other person unfortunate
enough to call you their friend.
So when I contact you again
and I require something.
you will comply with blind obedience.
You will comply with expediency.
Otherwise. my next bonfire
will be in California
over Rose Larkin's house.
Do you understand me?
Yes.
Good. Now get out.
Come on.
No. No. no.
He stays.
I lived up to my end of the arrangement.
That sort of integrity
should be rewarded. don't you think?
Peter.
Jay. Jay. you're gonna be okay.
What's going on?
Catherine.
Catherine. are you there?
Help!
Catherine. can you hear me?
Catherine.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm